diythemes.com 2019-12-09

# DIYthemes Privacy Policy

Effective December 21, 2012

### 1\. Our Commitment to Privacy

DIYthemes, LLC (“we, “our, or “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy. Online privacy is constantly evolving and DIYthemes plans to take all reasonable efforts to maintain up to date and effective online privacy standards and practices. By accessing diythemes.com or websites using the same TLD (the “Sites” or “Sites”), you are agreeing to the terms and condition of this Privacy Policy. DIYthemes may, from time to time, modify this Privacy Policy to reflect legal, technological and other developments. In that event, the changes will appear at this location.

### 2\. Information DIYthemes May Collect

The Privacy Policy applies to all information collected or submitted on the Site, and does not apply to information you may provide to us offline. We may collect an email address, a password of your choosing, and the recorded history of your activity on the Sites.

There are a variety of situations in which DIYthemes may collect personal information, such as when you register as a customer; purchase one of our products; download updates or white papers; respond to a marketing campaign; place orders on our website; or when you’re working with a DIYthemes service representative. In each of those situations, DIYthemes only collects the personal information required to meet your needs. Depending on the circumstances, we may ask for your name, company name, Internet domain name, email address, or other pertinent information.

DIYthemes uses your information to provide you with the services you have requested and better service. We may use your information to ensure compatibility, to communicate back to you, to inform you of and update you on services and benefits, and to manage and renew your agreement(s). DIYthemes will keep your personal information for as long as you are a registered user of our product(s) and thereafter, for no longer than is reasonably necessary for internal reporting and reconciliation purposes and to provide you with any feedback or information that you might request or require.

With the consent of our customers, DIYthemes posts customer testimonials on our website, which may contain personally identifiable information, such as the customer’s name or an avatar image associated with the customer.

If at any time you wish to remove your personal information from a DIYthemes website testimonial, please contact customer service.

We will not provide, sell, barter, or trade any information about you to/with any third parties, without your express permission, and above all, we will not sell this data to commercial users or make them available in any other form.

We may also need to share your personal information with other legal entities within DIYthemes. All such entities adhere to the DIYthemes Privacy Policy. From time to time, DIYthemes may provide personal information to law enforcement authorities or other third parties in response to a subpoena, an official inquiry, or as may be required in the case of national security. DIYthemes will not disclose your personal information to third parties for their own marketing purposes.

Whenever you visit the DIYthemes site, we may also automatically receive and record information in our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, your computer’s name, the type and version of your web browser, referrer addresses, and other generally-accepted log information. We may also record page views (hit counts) and other general statistical and tracking information.

This data enables us to become more familiar with which parts of the world visitors to our site come from, how often they visit, and which parts of the site they visit most often. We analyze this data for trends and statistics; we use them exclusively to help us better understand how our site is being used, to improve the value and user-friendliness of our website, and to detect any technical problems as early as possible.

### 3\. Children

DIYthemes does not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 13. In addition, no part of the Site is designed with the purpose of attracting any person under age 13.

### 4\. Cookies

Some pages on this site use “cookies,” which are small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk which help our servers recognize your computer when you visit again, so that it is easier for you to navigate on our website and make the best use of your visit. You should note that cookies cannot read data off of your hard drive. Your web browser may allow you to be notified when you are receiving a cookie, giving you the choice to accept it or not.

By not accepting cookies, you may not be able to access certain functionalities on this site. In particular, the “Remember my Password” feature for quick access to the DIYthemes application requires the use of cookies. The “Remember my password” feature is optional, and should you choose not to use it, you can still access the DIYthemes service normally.

### 5\. Links to Other Websites

The Site may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave the Site, you should note that we do not have any control over the other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### 6\. Questions or Concerns

If you have privacy-related questions that are not addressed here, please email us at diythemes@gmail.com or write us at:

DIYthemes, LLC  
PO Box 5429  
Austin, TX 78763
